University of Connecticut, Vice President and Chief Operating Officer Records 2006.0171
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Administrative Records, undated, 1908-1986
  - Employment - Clerks and others, 1921 (Box 10:, Folder 332)
  - Endowment Funds, 1977 (Box 10:, Folder 334-335)
  - Energy, 1973-1979 (Box 11:, Folder 336-338)
  - Energy, President's Advisory Committee on, 1979-1980 (Box 11:, Folder 339)
  - Enrollment, 1977-1978 (Box 11:, Folder 340)
  - Enrollment, 1979 (Box 11:, Folder 341)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1966-1977 (Box 11:, Folder 342)
  - Environmental Executive Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 11:, Folder 344)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 1974-1979 (Box 11:, Folder 345)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Committee on, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 346)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Office, 1973-1977 (Box 11:, Folder 347)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1979 (Box 11:, Folder 348)
  - Equipment, 1970-1975, 1979 (Box 11:, Folder 349)
  - Etherington Report, 1972 (Box 11:, Folder 350)
  - Etherington Report--Bookstore, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 83)
  - Etherington Report--Custodial, 1972 (Box 11:, Folder 351)
  - Etherington Report--Food Service, 1972-1973 (Box 11:, Folder 352)
  - Executive Records and Documents Section, 1974-1979 (Box 11:, Folder 353)
  - Exhibit Hall, 1969 (Box 11:, Folder 354)
  - Expand Associates, 1980 (Box 11:, Folder 355)
  - Expenditures and Revenues, 1918-1960 (Box 11:, Folder 356)
  - Explosive License, 1918 (Box 11:, Folder 357)
  - Extended and Continuing Education, 1976 (Box 11:, Folder 358)
  - Extension Funds, 1979 (Box 11:, Folder 359)
  - Facilities Use Restrictions, 1976-1977 (Box 11:, Folder 360)
  - Faculty Activities Survey, 1976 (Box 11:, Folder 361)
  - Faculty Alumni Center (Szabo File), 1965-1968 (Box 11:, Folder 362)
  - Faculty Alumni Center (Szabo File), 1969-1972 (Box 11:, Folder 363)
  - Faculty Center, 1967-1977 (Box 11:, Folder 364)
  - Faculty Evaluation System, 1974-1976 (Box 11:, Folder 365)
  - Faculty for Rational Alternatives, 1977 (Box 11:, Folder 366)
  - Faculty Load, 1961-1973 (Box 11:, Folder 367)
  - Faculty Standards Committee, 1969-1975 (Box 11:, Folder 368)
  - Fairfield University, 1967 (Box 11:, Folder 369)
  - Farwell House site, 1977-1979 (Box 11:, Folder 370)
  - Federal Funding for High Education, 1974-1977 (Box 11:, Folder 371)
  - Federation of Student and Service Organizations, 1974-1977 (Box 12:, Folder 372)
  - Federation of Student and Service Organizations, 1978-1979 (Box 12:, Folder 373)
  - Fee Increases, 1980 (Box 12:, Folder 374)
  - Fees, 1975-1977 (Box 12:, Folder 375)
  - Fees, 1976 (Box 12:, Folder 376)
  - Fees, 1977-1979 (Box 12:, Folder 377-378)
  - Fees, 1979 (Box 12:, Folder 379)
  - Fees, 1980-1981 (Box 12:, Folder 380)
  - Fees--laboratory, Field Trips, etc., 1974 (Box 12:, Folder 381)
  - Finance Advisory Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 12:, Folder 382)
  - Finance and Administration, Mission statements, undated, 1976 (Box 12:, Folder 383)
  - Finance and Control, 1967-1977 (Box 12:, Folder 384)
  - Finance and Control Procedures, 1968 (Box 12:, Folder 385)
  - Finance Committee, 1974 (Box 12:, Folder 386)
  - Finance Committee, Board of Trustees, 1972 (Box 12:, Folder 387)
  - Finance Committee for Student Government (Interim), 1973-1974 (Box 12:, Folder 388)
  - Financial Aid, 1978-1979 (Box 12:, Folder 389)
  - Fine Arts, 1970-1978 (Box 12:, Folder 390)
  - Fine Arts Facility (new), 1977-1978 (Box 12:, Folder 391)
  - Fire Truck, 1968-1978 (Box 12:, Folder 392)
  - FM Radio, 1966-1968 (Box 12:, Folder 393)
  - Food Service Companies, 1968-1974 (Box 12:, Folder 394)
  - Food Services, 1972-1977 (Box 12:, Folder 395)
  - Food Services, 1975-1976 (Box 12:, Folder 396)
  - Foundation, 1963-1977 (Box 12:, Folder 397-398)
  - Foundation, 1965-1979 (Box 12:, Folder 399)
  - Foundation, 1972-1976 (Box 13:, Folder 400)
  - Four Day Work Week, 1979 (Box 13:, Folder 401)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1964-1979 (Box 13:, Folder 402)
  - Fuel Oil, 1969-1974 (Box 13:, Folder 403)
  - Futures Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 404)
  - Gant, Edward V.--Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 13:, Folder 405)
  - Gas allocations, 1979 (Box 13:, Folder 406)
  - General Assembly districts, 1969 (Box 13:, Folder 407)
  - General Assembly, 1975-1979 (Box 13:, Folder 408)
  - Gifts, 1964-1977 (Box 13:, Folder 409)
  - Golf, 1965-1970 (Box OS, 13:, Folder 410)
  - Gold, Gold and Bernblum, 1971-1972 (Box 13:, Folder 411)
  - Good News, 1975-1979 (Box 13:, Folder 412)
  - Goodwin and Allyn Properties, 1975 (Box 13:, Folder 413)
  - Governor's Executive Orders, 1971-1977 (Box 13:, Folder 414)
  - Governor's Office, 1971-1976 (Box 13:, Folder 415)
  - Graduate Assistants, 1968-1979 (Box 13:, Folder 416)
  - Graduate School, 1971-1979 (Box 13:, Folder 417-418)
  - Graduate Stipends, 1974-1979 (Box 13:, Folder 419)
  - Graduate Student Council, 1970-1971 (Box 13:, Folder 420)
  - Gradute Students, Committee to Study the Status of, 1973-1974 (Box 13:, Folder 421)
  - Gradute Students, Committee to Study the Status of, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 422)
  - Grants and Contracts, 1977-1980 (Box 13:, Folder 423)
  - Greenhouse, 1979 (Box 13:, Folder 424)
  - Groton (Town and City), 1966-1978 (Box 13:, Folder 425)
  - Growth and Development Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 13:, Folder 426)
  - Gulley Hall, 1968-1975 (Box 13:, Folder 427)
  - Gurleyville Grist Mill Fund, Joshua's Trust, 1979 (Box 13:, Folder 428)
  - Guidelines, Committee on, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 429)
  - Handicapped Students and Requirements, 1971-1979 (Box 13:, Folder 430)
  - Hardee's, 1977-1978 (Box 13:, Folder 431)
  - Hartford Branch, 1974-1978 (Box 13:, Folder 432)
  - Hartford Properties, 1974-1976 (Box 13:, Folder 433)
  - Hartford Properties--6 Grand Street, 1974-1975 (Box 14:, Folder 434)
  - Hartford Properties--1380 Asylum Avenue, 1975-1977 (Box 14:, Folder 435)
  - Hartford Properties--1280 Asylum Avenue, 1971-1977 (Box 14:, Folder 436)
  - Hartford Properties owned by UConn, 1974-1975 (Box 14:, Folder 437)
  - Hartford Seminary Property, 1975-1978 (Box 14:, Folder 438)
  - Hartford Seminary--School of Law, 1977-1979 (Box 14:, Folder 439-440)
  - Hawley Armoury, 1976 (Box 14:, Folder 441)
  - Health Care program, Committee to study the need, feasibility and costs of establishing a prepaid, comprehensive, 1974 (Box 14:, Folder 442)
  - Health Center
    - Access Road, 1968 (Box 14:, Folder 443)
    - Accounting, 1970-1972 (Box 14:, Folder 444)
    - Accounts Receivable, 1972-1974 (Box 14:, Folder 445)
    - Assistant Vice President, 1971-1976 (Box 14:, Folder 446)
    - Admission of students, 1972 (Box 14:, Folder 447)
    - Administration, 1969 (Box 14:, Folder 448)
    - Agreements, 1973 (Box 14:, Folder 449)
    - Architect, 1965-1966 (Box 14:, Folder 450)
    - Architect--Kling, 1964-1972 (Box 14:, Folder 451)
    - Attorney General, 1965-1966 (Box 14:, Folder 452)
    - Audit, 1969-1972 (Box 14:, Folder 453)
    - Auditorium, 1968 (Box 14:, Folder 454)
    - Autonomy, 1971 (Box 14:, Folder 455)
    - Blue Cross, 1971 (Box 14:, Folder 456)
    - Budget, 1960-1975 (Box 14:, Folder 457)
    - Budget, Operating, 1969-1971 (Box 14:, Folder 458)
    - Budget, Operating, 1972-1973 (Box 14:, Folder 459)
    - Budget, Operating Request, 1971-1973 (Box 14:, Folder 460)
    - Budget, Operating Request, 1973-1974 (Box 14:, Folder 461)
    - Building Occupancy, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 462)
    - Burgdorf Health Center, 1970 (Box 14:, Folder 463)
    - Bus, 1972 (Box 14:, Folder 464)
    - Business Office, 1972 (Box 14:, Folder 465)
    - By-Laws, undated (Box 14:, Folder 466)
    - Capital Expenditures, 1971 (Box 14:, Folder 467)
    - Capital Financing, 1971 (Box 14:, Folder 468)
    - Capital Request, 1969-1971 (Box 14:, Folder 469)
    - Capital Request, 1972-1973 (Box 14:, Folder 470)
    - Capital Request, 1973-1974 (Box 14:, Folder 471)
    - Change orders, 1971 (Box 14:, Folder 472)
    - Commission for Higher Education study, 1972 (Box 14:, Folder 473)
    - Committee, 1974 (Box 14:, Folder 474)
    - Computers, 1973 (Box 14:, Folder 475)
    - Construction, 1968-1975 (Box 14:, Folder 476)
    - Construction Time Table, 1969 (Box 14:, Folder 477)
    - Controller's Office, 1972 (Box 14:, Folder 478)
    - Convalescent Care, 1966 (Box 14:, Folder 479)
    - Data processing, 1971 (Box 14:, Folder 480)
    - Delinquent accounts, 1973-1975 (Box 14:, Folder 481)
    - Demand Billing, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 482)
    - Discount Policy, undated (Box 14:, Folder 483)
    - Drainage problem, 1972 (Box 14:, Folder 484)
    - Easements, 1967-1972 (Box 14:, Folder 485)
    - Electricity, 1965-1966 (Box 14:, Folder 486)
    - Electricity, 1965-1968 (Box 14:, Folder 487)
    - Energy System, 1965-1966 (Box 14:, Folder 488)
    - Equipment, 1969 (Box 14:, Folder 489)
    - Farmington Hospital, 1971 (Box 14:, Folder 490)
    - Farmington (Town of), 1966 (Box 14:, Folder 491)
    - Federal Fund applications, 1965-1972 (Box 14:, Folder 492)
    - Fees, 1966-1974 (Box 14:, Folder 493)
    - Financial statements, 1972-1973 (Box 14:, Folder 494)
    - Fire Insurance, 1973 (Box 14:, Folder 495)
    - Fire Protection, 1968-1969 (Box 14:, Folder 496)
    - Food Service, 1965-1974 (Box 14:, Folder 497)
    - Foundation, 1971 (Box 14:, Folder 498)
    - Furnishings, 1974 (Box 14:, Folder 499)
    - Fund Raising, 1965-1966 (Box 14:, Folder 500)
    - Future Plans, 1972 (Box 15:, Folder 501)
    - Gas, 1961-1969 (Box 15:, Folder 502)
    - Gorsline, Lester, 1964-1966 (Box 15:, Folder 503)
    - Grants, 1971-1972 (Box 15:, Folder 504)
    - Grievance Procedure, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 505)
    - Group Practice, 1972 (Box 15:, Folder 506)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1966 (Box 15:, Folder 507)
    - Highway Planning, 1967 (Box 15:, Folder 508)
    - Hospital, 1972 (Box 15:, Folder 509)
    - House Staff, 1971 (Box 15:, Folder 510)
    - Laundry, 1965-1969 (Box 15:, Folder 511)
    - Leases, 1970 (Box 15:, Folder 512)
    - Leming, James, 1972 (Box 15:, Folder 513)
    - Licenses, 1974 (Box 15:, Folder 514)
    - Long Range Plans, 1970 (Box 15:, Folder 515)
    - Maher, Edward, 1966-1970 (Box 15:, Folder 516)
    - Maintenance, 1971 (Box 15:, Folder 517)
    - Master Site Plan, 1974 (Box 15:, Folder 518)
    - McCook Hospital
      - 1967-1975 (Box 15:, Folder 519)
      - Audit, 1970-1972 (Box 15:, Folder 520)
      - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 15:, Folder 521)
      - E & E Management Letter, 1974 (Box 15:, Folder 522)
      - Emergency Exit, 1971 (Box 15:, Folder 523)
      - Move to Farmington, 1974 (Box 15:, Folder 524)
      - Prison Ward, 1972 (Box 15:, Folder 525)
      - Subsidy, 1972 (Box 15:, Folder 526)
    - Medical Education, 1971 (Box 15:, Folder 527)
    - Medical Health Services, 1974 (Box 15:, Folder 528)
    - Meyer, Strong & Jones, 1964-1966 (Box 15:, Folder 529)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1966-1970 (Box 15:, Folder 530)
    - New Jersey Report, 1970 (Box 15:, Folder 531)
    - Nursing, 1968-1969 (Box 15:, Folder 532)
    - Organization, 1972 (Box 15:, Folder 533)
    - Parking, 1973-1974 (Box 15:, Folder 534)
    - Payroll Audit, 1972-1973 (Box 15:, Folder 535)
    - Phase A, 1970 (Box 15:, Folder 536)
    - Phase B, 1972 (Box 15:, Folder 537)
    - Phase C, 1972 (Box 15:, Folder 538)
    - Physical Plant, 1966-1972 (Box 15:, Folder 539)
    - Plans (images), undated (Box 15:, Folder 540)
    - Prefabricated Buildings, 1967-1970 (Box 15:, Folder 541)
    - Public Utilities Commission, 1966 (Box 15:, Folder 542)
    - Public Works Department, 1966 (Box 15:, Folder 543)
    - Real Estate, 1965-1974 (Box 15:, Folder 544)
    - Renovations, 1974 (Box 15:, Folder 545)
    - Research, 1969-1971 (Box 15:, Folder 546)
    - Research Academic Wing, 1968-1973 (Box 15:, Folder 547)
    - Scholarships, 1972 (Box 15:, Folder 548)
    - School of Dentistry, 1970-1972 (Box 15:, Folder 549)
    - School of Medicine, 1967 (Box 15:, Folder 550)
    - School of Medicine Council, undated (Box 15:, Folder 551)
    - Security, 1966-1971 (Box 15:, Folder 552)
    - Senate, 1971 (Box 15:, Folder 553)
    - Sewer, 1966 (Box 15:, Folder 554)
    - Space, 1967-1976 (Box 15:, Folder 555)
    - Speed Space, Inc., 1970 (Box 15:, Folder 556)
    - Statutes, 1963 (Box 15:, Folder 557)
    - Storrs, undated (Box 15:, Folder 558)
    - Student and staff housing, 1968-1969 (Box 15:, Folder 559)
    - Telephones, 1970 (Box 15:, Folder 560)
    - Temporary Buildings, 1970 (Box 15:, Folder 561)
    - Town Planning, 1971 (Box 15:, Folder 562)
    - Traffic, 1967 (Box 15:, Folder 563)
    - Vice President, undated (Box 15:, Folder 564)
    - Water, 1965-1967 (Box 15:, Folder 565)
  - Health Service Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 15:, Folder 566)
  - Health Services, 1964-1977 (Box 15:, Folder 567)
  - Health Serivces--Branches, 1976 (Box 15:, Folder 568)
  - Higher Education Grants to Branches, Title IV Part A, 1968 (Box 15:, Folder 569)
  - Historic District Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 15:, Folder 570)
  - History of Connecticut Agricultural College, Edwina Whitney, [1916] (Box 15:, Folder 571)
  - History of UConn Project, 1978 (Box 15:, Folder 572)
  - Houses, 1976-1979 (Box 16:, Folder 573)
  - Houses (university) Quitclaim Deeds, 1976-1977 (Box 16:, Folder 574)
  - Housing and Food Services, 1973-1975 (Box 16:, Folder 575)
  - Housing Committee (Boyce), 1975-1977 (Box 16:, Folder 576)
  - Housing--Elderly, 1977 (Box 16:, Folder 577)
  - Housing--Married Students, 1973 (Box 16:, Folder 578)
  - Housing Policy, Advisory Committee on, 1975-1977 (Box 16:, Folder 579)
  - Houley, Robert D. (State Senator), 1971-1972 (Box 16:, Folder 580)
  - Human Rights and Opportunities, 1969-1980 (Box 16:, Folder 581)
  - Human Rights and Opportunities, Council on, 1976 (Box 16:, Folder 582)
  - Human Rights and Opportunities, Council on--Community Involvement Program, 1968-1973 (Box 16:, Folder 583)
  - Identification cards and numbers, 1970-1978 (Box 16:, Folder 584)
  - Inter-Area Resident's Council (IARC), 1976-1977 (Box 16:, Folder 585)
  - Inauguration (DiBiaggio, Babbidge) (Box 16:, Folder 586)
  - Indiana--Correspondence, 1966-1973 (Box 17:, Folder 625)
  - Indirect costs, 1977-1979 (Box 16:, Folder 587)
  - Individual Time Analysis, 1976 (Box 16:, Folder 588)
  - Infirmary, Sanitation, 1965-1976 (Box 16:, Folder 589)
  - Insitute of Cellular Biology, Executive Committee, 1974 (Box 16:, Folder 590)
  - Institute of Materials Science, 1971-1977 (Box 16:, Folder 591)
  - Institute of Materials Science, 1979 (Box 16:, Folder 592)
  - Institute of Materials Science Committee, 1974 (Box 16:, Folder 593)
  - Institute of Water Resources, 1965-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 626)
  - Institute of World Affairs Advisory Committee, 1973 (Box 16:, Folder 594)
  - Institutional Policy Committee
    - 1976 September 10 (Box 16:, Folder 595)
    - 1978 July 14 (Box 16:, Folder 596)
    - 1978 September 8 (Box 16:, Folder 597)
    - 1978 October 13 (Box 16:, Folder 598)
    - 1979 (Box 16:, Folder 599)
    - 1979 January 12 (Box 16:, Folder 600)
    - 1979 February 9 (Box 16:, Folder 601)
    - 1979 March 16 (Box 16:, Folder 602)
    - 1979 April 20 (Box 16:, Folder 603)
    - 1979 May 18 (Box 16:, Folder 604)
    - 1979 June 8 (Box 16:, Folder 605)
    - 1979 July 13 (Box 16:, Folder 606)
    - 1979 November 10 (Box 16:, Folder 607)
    - 1979 December 8 (Box 16:, Folder 608)
  - Institutional Research, 1975-1976 (Box 16:, Folder 609)
  - Institutional Research, 1978-1979 (Box 16:, Folder 610)
  - Insurance, 1974-1979 (Box 16:, Folder 611)
  - Interest, 1908-1925 (Box 16:, Folder 612)
  - Internal Audit, 1972-1979 (Box 16:, Folder 613)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1969-1978 (Box 16:, Folder 614)
  - International Education and Development, 1979 (Box 16:, Folder 615)
  - International Programs, 1979 (Box 16:, Folder 616)
  - Internships, 1980-1981 (Box 16:, Folder 617)
  - Investments, 1970, 1979 (Box 16:, Folder 618)
  - Insurance--Automobile, 1969-1973 (Box 16:, Folder 619)
  - Insurance--Faculty and Staff, 1969-1971 (Box 16:, Folder 620)
  - Insurance--Major Medical, 1971-1974 (Box 16:, Folder 621)
  - Insurance--Property, 1971, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 622)
  - Insurance--Student, 1971-1973 (Box 17:, Folder 623)
  - Inventory, 1967-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 624)
  - Job descriptions and Organizational Chart, 1973-1975 (Box 17:, Folder 628)
  - Joint Legislative Committee, 1970 (Box 17:, Folder 629)
  - Joint Operations Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 630-631)
  - Joint POlicy Committee, 1968 (Box 17:, Folder 632)
  - Junior Year in France Program, 1974-1978 (Box 17:, Folder 633)
  - Kammer, Harry J., 1974-1979 (Box 17:, Folder 634)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1962-1964 (Box 17:, Folder 635)
  - Kirby Mill, 1979 (Box 17:, Folder 636)
  - Kitty Hawk Unlimited, 1974 (Box 17:, Folder 637)
  - Kellner-Oshny Associates, 1970 (Box 17:, Folder 638)
  - Lakeside Apartments, 1961-1979 (Box 17:, Folder 639)
  - Land Survey, 1923 (Box 17:, Folder 640)
  - Layoff Activity, 1979-1981 (Box 17:, Folder 641)
  - Leasing Procedures, 1975-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 642)
  - Leased Space, 1968-1976 (Box 17:, Folder 643)
  - Legislative Data, 1965-1969 (Box 17:, Folder 644)
  - Legislative Problems, 1969 (Box 17:, Folder 645)
  - Legislative Procedures, undated (Box 17:, Folder 646)
  - Legislative Public Relations, 1969 (Box 17:, Folder 647)
  - Legislative Request, 1969-1971 (Box 17:, Folder 648)
  - Legislative Request, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 649)
  - Legislative Work Papers, 1971-1973 (Box 17:, Folder 650)
  - Legislators, 1968-1976 (Box 17:, Folder 651)
  - Legislators--Student admissions, 1968-1969 (Box 17:, Folder 652)
  - Legislature
    - 1969 (Box 17:, Folder 653)
    - 1971-1973 (Box 17:, Folder 654)
    - 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 655)
    - 1974 (Box 17:, Folder 656)
    - 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 657)
    - 1976 (Box 17:, Folder 658)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 659)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 17:, Folder 660)
    - Obsolete Bills, 1971-1973 (Box 17:, Folder 661)
    - Study of General Assembly, 1967 (Box 17:, Folder 662)
    - Task Force, 1970 (Box 17:, Folder 663)
  - Library, 1974-1979 (Box 18:, Folder 664-665)
  - Library, Art Acquisitions Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 18:, Folder 666)
  - Library, Ad hoc Committee, 1969 (Box 18:, Folder 667)
  - Library, Subcommittee on Professional Staff, 1974 (Box 18:, Folder 668)
  - License, Radio, 1924 (Box 18:, Folder 669)
  - Liquor on Campus, 1972-1974 (Box 18:, Folder 670)
  - Living-Learning Center, 1974 (Box 18:, Folder 671)
  - Longevity Payments, 1967-1977 (Box 18:, Folder 672)
  - Lovejoy (L.C.) Report #1, Public Salary Administration Research, 1965 (Box 18:, Folder 673)
  - Mail Service, 1968-1977 (Box 18:, Folder 674)
  - Mail Services, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 675)
  - Main Street Management, 1977 (Box 18:, Folder 676)
  - Management Information Systems, 1976-1979 (Box 18:, Folder 677)
  - Mansfield (Town of), 1975-1977 (Box 18:, Folder 678)
  - Mansfield Businessmen's Association, 1975 (Box 18:, Folder 679)
  - Mansfield Fire Department, 1963 (Box 18:, Folder 680)
  - Mansfield State Training School, 1968-1977 (Box 18:, Folder 681)
  - Mansfield Historical Society, 1972 (Box 18:, Folder 682)
  - Marine Science, 1968-1974 (Box 18:, Folder 683)
  - MBA Program, 1973-1974 (Box 18:, Folder 684)
  - MPA Program, 1974 (Box 18:, Folder 685)
  - McDonald's Corporation, 1975 (Box 18:, Folder 686)
  - McKenna, John F., University Attorney, 1977-1979 (Box 18:, Folder 687)
  - Mediator--Constitution, 1919 (Box 18:, Folder 688)
  - Medical-Dental School, 1960-1963 (Box 18:, Folder 689)
  - Military Equipment, 1924 (Box 18:, Folder 690)
  - Minority Affairs Office, 1975-1977 (Box 18:, Folder 691)
  - Mirror Lake, 1971 (Box 18:, Folder 692)
  - Mission Statement, 1975 (Box 18:, Folder 693)
  - Moreland, Wallace, 1966-1972 (Box 18:, Folder 694)
  - Moss Survey (Box 18:, Folder 695)
  - Motor Pool, 1969-1976 (Box 18:, Folder 696)
  - Music Department, 1966-1977 (Box 18:, Folder 697)
  - Nanos Property, 1973 (Box 18:, Folder 698)
  - Napolitano, Frank, 1974 (Box 18:, Folder 699)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers (NACUBO), 1973-1979 (Box 18:, Folder 700)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC), 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 701)
  - National Medal of Science Committee, 1974 (Box 18:, Folder 702)
  - National Science Foundation, 1977 (Box 18:, Folder 703)
  - National Defense Student Loan Program, 1968-1978 (Box 18:, Folder 704)
  - Natural Areas, Committee on, 1972 (Box 18:, Folder 705)
  - Naugatuck Valley Regional Center, 1975 (Box 18:, Folder 706)
  - Needs for Buildings and Improvements, 1925-1927 (Box 18:, Folder 707)
  - Network College, 1975 (Box 18:, Folder 708-709)
  - New England Research Application Center (NERAC), 1968-1979 (Box 19:, Folder 710)
  - New England Board of Higher Education, 1971-1975 (Box 19:, Folder 711)
  - Nutmeg State Employees Credit Union, 1975 (Box 19:, Folder 712)
  - Occupational Health and Safety Act, 1972-1979 (Box 19:, Folder 713)
  - Ombudsman, 1970-1975 (Box 19:, Folder 714)
  - Organizational and Functional charts, 1961-1968 (Box 19:, Folder 715)
  - Orientation Program, 1975 (Box 19:, Folder 716)
  - Paparazzo Development Corporation, 1967 (Box 19:, Folder 717)
  - Parking and Traffic, 1974-1977 (Box 19:, Folder 718)
  - Parking Lots, 1963-1964 (Box 19:, Folder 719)
  - Patents, 1972-1976 (Box 19:, Folder 720)
  - Patho-Biology Department, 1974-1978 (Box 19:, Folder 721)
  - Payroll, 1969-1977 (Box 19:, Folder 722)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1967-1968 (Box 19:, Folder 723)
  - Perkin-Elmer, 1980 (Box 19:, Folder 724)
  - Permit, 2nd class mailing (Egg Laying Reports), 1926 (Box 19:, Folder 725)
  - Permit, Sewer Line, 1929-1930 (Box 19:, Folder 726)
  - Permit, Water Still, 1929 (Box 19:, Folder 727)
  - Permit, Whiskey Purchase, 1923 (Box 19:, Folder 728)
  - Personnel Advisory Board (State), 1967-1975 (Box 19:, Folder 729)
  - Philosophy Department, 1967 (Box 19:, Folder 730)
  - Physical Plant Division, 1967-1977 (Box 19:, Folder 731-732)
  - Physical Plant, 1977-1978 (Box 19:, Folder 733)
  - Physical Plant, 1978-1979 (Box 19:, Folder 734)
  - Physical Plant, Audit and Investigation, 1972-1974 (Box 19:, Folder 735)
  - Placement, 1974 (Box 19:, Folder 736)
  - Planning, 1976-1977 (Box 19:, Folder 737)
  - Planning, 1980 (Box 19:, Folder 738)
  - Political Activities, Employee, 1975 (Box 19:, Folder 739)
  - Office of Policy and Management, 1978-1979 (Box 19:, Folder 740)
  - Policy Letters (Campus-wide), 1977-1979 (Box 19:, Folder 741)
  - Policy Research, Office of, 1979 (Box 19:, Folder 742)
  - Pomeroy House, Waterbury, 1972-1974 (Box 19:, Folder 743)
  - President Appointed Committees/Commissions, 1970 (Box 19:, Folder 744)
  - Prioritized list of positions (Budget request), 1980-1981 (Box 19:, Folder 745)
  - Provost Search, 1974 (Box 19:, Folder 746)
  - Puerto Rican Center, Advisory Board, 1975 (Box 19:, Folder 747)
  - Puerto Rican Center, Director Search Committee, 1975 (Box 19:, Folder 748)
  - Radio and Television Center, Advisory Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 19:, Folder 749)
  - Rathskellar Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 19:, Folder 750)
  - Report, President, 1927 (Box 19:, Folder 751)
  - Reports, 1969-1974 (Box 19:, Folder 752)
  - Report to the Board of Trustees, Capitol Building Program, 1972 (Box 20:, Folder 753)
  - Research Strategies Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 20:, Folder 754)
  - Salaries Presentation, 1974-1975 (Box 20:, Folder 755)
  - School of Business Administration, 1970-1977 (Box 20:, Folder 756)
  - School of Education, 1971-1977 (Box 20:, Folder 757)
  - School of Engineering, 1972-1977 (Box 20:, Folder 758)
  - School of Home Economics and Family Studies, 1972-1976 (Box 20:, Folder 759)
  - School of Law, 1967-1979 (Box 20:, Folder 760-762)